So look friends, this is our insurance
paper, this photo sticker of it, brother, the
insurance had come, so an
alert comes on the insurance side from Hero, which
we would have received, then
you will get a message from there separately and secondly, you are
seeing Heroine in Vivo from Hero here,
but they said that
your special insurance will be renewed for around 121400, so
what will happen to this old insurance paper that you have, the same
time, the same registration number before the number plate, through
SMS, friends, how are you all, so friend,
this is a very important thing for our bike today, brother, brother,
in which you have to
give an update, like the
insurance of our bike,
brother, see what is the relief, it has to be
reviewed every year, okay, that
means it has to be renewed every year, will it
remain in the new, the first
party, third party, they have to be
renewed, okay, so
for that, look in the big or at least
remember yourself that you will not have it on this date,
otherwise, brother, an alert comes on the message from
Hero, okay, which
we  It has been received in our mobile phone
which is kept on the back key, okay, so
some messages have been received in it, so brother, let me
also show you what kind of
message channel is there, okay, you also get an
idea, you will get an idea,
okay, so brother, our insurance which has been renewed is going to
expire on the 25th,
but the day on which this video is being posted, brother,
it is a Sunday, okay, so brother, brother, I will have to get
it renewed, okay, then
go to the showroom and show you what is written in the message, brother,
and brother, I have already
talked to them on the phone about
how much the insurance will cost, brother,
okay, we will
also
talk to you about the insurance expenses, okay,
and by the way, if you want to
know anything else about the insurance, brother, you want to see how
we got the papers, brother, in the bike's account, okay, then
brother, open the description box and
scroll down,
you will see the video, okay, so
first of all, brother, the message about your insurance,
brother, that has come, regarding the new one.
Let's see brother, does it send an alert brother, brother the Hero
company will send you an alert for insurance
every year whenever your
insurance has to be renewed, okay, so let's see that message, so
see friends, this is
our insurance paper, this is its
photostat, okay, let me show you
its validity from 25-9-2022, the time
is also written from 958 32 and the validity
will be on midnight 25-9-2017, now you will
think that brother, it is going to
expire on 2017, so how are you getting this message done so soon, so
look at one thing, look
down, see what
is written here, this number number, all this will go
up, okay, so look here, here
it is written, look at this Audi policy,
from 26-9-2022 to 25-9-2000 23, so brother, this is
our renewal brother message, okay, you have come
regarding this thing, okay and you see the rest,
this will be new on 25th, then  This will happen in 2025
and then in 2026 this will happen in 2017, okay, so
this is given in different terms and
in the above you ask
what all will be done and what all will not be done,
so look, these limitations are there, the
complete details of the policy are written, okay,
if you want you can read them, okay,
if you do not understand then you can
tell us, we will talk about it in detail in some other detailed video,
okay, so
friends, this is our message box
in the mobile, okay, so see, we also got a message of this type for
renewing the insurance, okay,
you can see it, you will get a message from Pawan
separately, okay, which is registered in RTO,
so
you will get a message from there separately and secondly, you can
see this Heroine from Hero here,
this will come, and brother, IDFC
Bank, look in this, a lot of
alerts are being given, about 3-4 alert
messages have already come, one, two or three of them are from
Hero.  Also and from there side, first of all
this message came
yesterday, you can see
what is written in it, look at the message,
it is written from Heroine, Dear
Customer Insurance of Splendor Plus X D
RS Casting on 25/09 2023, so you
know it is written that your mobile should be
linked in it, so what do you have to do for this brother, your
mobile should be linked with Aadhar card,
linked with PAN card and holder ID should be
linked with driving license, then
you can do KYC by going to this link or you
can also do this for renewal policy or you
can do it directly by going to your showroom, see it is written in Hindi also,
you can see it above,
its
price is being given for tax, your special price is
not given here, okay, you will have to get it renewed
or call the agency, okay, then it will get
locked, call the showroom,
okay, so something like this, brother, there is one more thing,
you should look carefully, okay, it is related
to PUC, see this thing, from there it is
written kid  Attention Virendra Singh, I mean it is
not in my father's name, it is ours,
this certificate of vehicle, vehicle
number bill expires on 1st October 2013, if you
want brother PUC, what does it mean,
you guys will think that your brother has
not made PUC, then what is this PUC
message about, okay, so
in its bigger brother, I will have to know a little more,
okay, after going to the showroom, then I will
tell you the details, okay, we will talk about it in a one-two minute
video in some other video,
okay, this has come from there regarding PUC as well,
brother
for renewing the insurance,
okay, so this is it, now let's talk about its cost, I
mean, how much will it cost to renew it, brother,
how much will it cost to get it renewed,
okay, so let's go to the bike, let me
tell you that our new
insurance is going to be, okay, as soon as we got the message,
brother, we first
called the showroom people directly, they told us that
we have received a message like this, brother,
your insurance has to be renewed
Brother, it will expire on the 25th, it will be one year old,
so they said there is
no such thing, you can go to the showroom, okay, then
your renewal will be done, brother,
your expenses, brother they had
told us, the insurance renewal expense, we took it,
they said that
your expenses are going to be around 121400,
okay, so for now we will go to the same showroom,
okay, take the bike, you can see that the
bike is completely ready and we will also take the mobile, we will
show them the message that we have received from the insurance, okay, and
brother, our EMI is also about to expire,
okay, with whom it is going to be completed,
brother, there is a separate process for
terminating it, they will also
come after asking what is the matter, there is no detail,
then they will tell you, it is expected that what they have
told us, okay, and
brother, the expenses of the insurance renewal,
they had told the same 1200, they had
told between 12 to 1400, okay, they had
said something that when the insurance is
renewed, you will have  What will happen to this old
insurance paper,
he said that you have to keep this old
insurance paper
with you as a proof, the original
insurance which you got earlier, then the
new one which you will renew, you will get it
maybe for 127 or for four-five rupees, okay, so the
new paper which you will get will be the
insurance paper, you have to
keep it with you, okay, you have to
keep that paper with you, so
he had told us this much on the call also, we will find out the rest of the
details by going to the showroom, so
friends, these are your
lovely comments brother, this Ramakant
brother is asking brother, how much did
you get the bike for, brother, I had told you that I had
financed it on us, okay and brother
Divyanshu Kumar Rathore brother is asking
what has he written in it, brother, let's
see, he says brother, can you install a simple button on the Discover 100cc
digital meter bike,
please brother, reply brother, install a switch button in your bike,
all four indicators together
in a gel digital meter, you can install a simple button,
brother, please  Reply Bajaj Discover so brother,
I will reply to you immediately right away
okay brother, I did not pay attention
brother, brother, I mean on your comment, okay, then I will reply right away
brother, by the way, if I tell you right now, brother,
now you can think, there is no problem, okay,
only the assembly changes
[music]
brother, at what price do you
get this brother, so brother,
Suraj Kumar has already told, thank you so match brother
for telling in details, so that is the same thank you
and brother, this brother asks Radhe Radhe
Krishna ji, what are you doing about my Splendor
bike,
my Splendor bike has talent, everything is
available, don't worry brother, try it carefully, then everything will work, I
mean
brother, we had shown in the video that the oil well
portion is available, brother, he told that if you
shake it in this manner, then everything will work, no problem, there are more
comments, let's see,
Amarjeet brother, tell me one thing, brother, he had made a
very long comment, okay, we will
see those as well, what is this,
new block brother, this brother, he has done it, let's see, it is
good, someone's dream has come true,
someone's dream has come true
[Music] Can you
see it or else let me tell you
it asks if the registration number is there before the number plate, the
SMS comes or not so
brother I will tell you brother brother the SMS comes
brother is Narendra Singh this brother asks
these were your lovely
comments okay so friends today only I had to
give you information brother I also
received the message so I thought brother I should inform you as well
you should also be informed
brothers whatever number of people have
brother check your bike brother if it has been more than 1 year and you have
not got the insurance renewed, if you have forgotten then brother
check it by opening the message box as I
showed you you will definitely get some messages like this
okay and for loan also there are enough
messages brother from wherever you get the
finance done now yes from the bank okay then
check it once brother if you
believe me it is very important to get the insurance renewed
brother otherwise you will become a bad fan
if the police catch you then okay so
today we just learned that brother
for insurance brother an alert message comes
on your mobile number whoever has registered his  If it is there then there is nothing else, otherwise
if you have any query
regarding the video, that is regarding insurance, then brother, there is a
video in the description, watch it,
I have shown all the papers, otherwise we will meet
in some other video, till then
[Music]